Yo yo what's going on everybody? I hope
all of you are well. In this video I
want to show you the actionable steps
after you get a winning ad. So you can
kind of see right here uh I launched
this ad on this day at ad number two is
what we're calling it. You know I have a
lot of stuff uh blurred out here and ad
number two slowly became top spender.
And what I did is I add this actual ad
set name number three. This batch of ads
that align really closely with ad number
two and it started helping it in the ad
account efficiency right
by decreasing the CPA at an ad account
level. Um now these numbers are a little
bit skewed because this first day was
actually during an ad account ban. So if
you look up here like you're like oh why
are you like not spending a lot? I got
banned the same day. So I had to go on a
new ad account uh manually increase my
DSL and then you know you understand
like it takes one or two days for your
ad account to recover. Um, so basically
as my ad account was recovering day two
I actually hit a new winning ad and that
hence why you know you see number two
like the rorowaz on this ad when I when
I when I uploaded it right the same day
I upload a new batch you know it got
spent I was like oh it got spent first
day this is a really good sign and the
second day it almost took top spend you
know I was scaling up this ad account
day two um and then you can see you know
day three and day four you know it got
scaled back to like normal numbers or
relatively normal numbers
um you know I still need still like have
to show you like I scale it further and
further and further etc. Um, but you can
[clears throat] see like what like what
this entire thing goes goes into. And I
want to talk about like what actually
happens, right? How can we create this
funnel when we have this winning ad,
right? And what happened was this ad was
a unique angle, an angle that I had
never tested before, right? Number two,
and it immediately soaked up spend. I
was like, "Oh shit." Okay, this ad is,
you know, a new angle and that's why
it's getting this much spend because we
finally validated this angle. We put in
here, oh, it validated immediately.
Great. This angle works. Let's look at
this ad on a, you know, a very like
nitty-gritty basis. What what was
everything in this ad, right? Like what
did we miss? And I knew that this ad
number two was solution aware setting to
a listical, right? And I was like, oh
[\h__\h] Okay, so this ad is a solution
aware ad, henceforth why it's kind of
towards the top of the spend. You know,
it's towards the middle of the funnel.
Um, and you know, like if you guys like
everyone's aware of like the five states
of awareness, right? Um, I rarely ever
go into this unaware audience. It's
really hard to crack that. And problem
aware is pretty hard as well, but it's
able to be cracked and I've cracked it
before. In fact, that's what this ad
here is, right? This problem aware ad.
But this solutionware ad in my market is
pretty [\h__\h] big and it's like if you
have this problem in my market, you're
going to be moved into the solutionware
solution aware state pretty frequently,
like pretty pretty quickly, I would say.
And so it's able to really be a really
like really big TAM because the solution
aware market is super big. So, this
solution aware ad took top spend at top
of funnel
and the ad account, right? And what we
did was basically I was like, "Oh [\h__\h]
okay, this ad is now my top spender or
it's going to be my top spender." You
know, it's getting a lot of spend. I was
like, "Fuck, let's immediately let's
push priority on these ads." I told my
editors like, "Let's get this batch out
tomorrow." Um, instead of like, you
know, going in Q. I was like, "No, let's
get this batch out tomorrow cuz I really
think we've hit a new winning angle
here." And that's exactly what happened.
Um, so basically number two, this adset
number two was sending to was a
solutionware ad here sending to a
listical, right? A five, if you guys
aren't aware of listical, it's a five
reasons why you need to buy XYZ. It's
like, oh [\h__\h] Okay. And we've we've
obviously met them at Solutionware and
we've pushed them further down the
funnel into Productware in this ad,
right? Obviously, like that's what we do
when we meet them at Solutionware, we
need to push them down. If we meet them
at problemware, we have to push them
down. We meet them under, we have to
push them down, right? Um, so we pushed
them down from solution to productware
and they're obviously aware of our
product. And I noticed I didn't really
address many objections, right? And I
didn't do a lot of the offer stacking
things in this ad. I was like, okay,
let's take this exact same angle with
the exact same concept of what's going
on, okay? Like like in this ad, I'll use
a certain let's say voice in the voice
over. So like they remember this voice,
okay? And I use this and I use a
relatively same hook. So they're like
they're like, "Oh, I remember this."
Right? And we just start at the procare
and we immediately hit all the product
objections that they have and you're
like okay like what what product
objections do you hit? Like how do you
know what product objections to hit?
Like this requires research of course,
right? Like you should have your full
[\h__\h] sheet of like okay these are all
the product objections. So I hit all the
product objections along with that
future pace positively what effect that
this you know product will have on their
life. Okay. So it's like oh like all
these things will happen right? And then
I had loss aversion, which if you guys
aren't familiar with loss aversion, it's
just simply the concept of like you have
this I hate to use these buzzwords, but
a cognitive bias of I would rather not
lose than win, right? It's like if like
so like on a day-to-day basis, right?
Like if we look at this, okay, when I
scale up here and like okay, like I get
my ad account back, I'm scaling up back
to normal numbers, like it feels fine,
right? But then if let's say on the
fifth day I have really bad ROS on all
these ads and my profit margin goes down
that's going to feel really shitty and
it's going to feel a lot shittier than
it felt good when I was just scaling
everything up right so um that it's like
it's like if you make $10 right it
doesn't feel that good whereas if you
lose $10 it's like damn I lost $10 right
and it's the same thing with ecom like
every day I'm making a few thousand net
now if I break even randomly on a day
and I go from making a few thousand a
day to then break even. It's kind of
like a [\h__\h] that sucks, right? So then I
I'm I'm showing them, you know, this
loss aversion. What happens if they
don't take action along with I'm sending
them straight to the PDP because they're
already super warm. They're already
aware of the product. I I've listed out
all their objections. Bang, they're
gone. I I've positively future paced
their entire life. Bang, we got this.
And then I'm like, "Oh [\h__\h] like here's
what happen if you don't take action."
Right? This is a very very common
aviatorial concept. Um and it's like,
"Oh [\h__\h] here's what happens if you
don't take action." If you go through
aviators that are good, like if you go
like if you go to like get hooked, okay,
um it's it's a great software. If you go
to get hooked and you go to like
performance four or five out of five,
you look in the supplement niche and you
click the the the URLs, you're going to
see a lot of aviatorals and those are
good avitorials obviously because the
ads are performing really well. You can
break down towards the close section
what they're doing. You know, they're
doing a lot of this. And so I was like,
okay, let's just take what the [\h__\h]
you know, like like the concept of an
avitorial, right, and just apply that to
this ad, right? And it's just like
here's all the product objections. Like
they're already they've already been
revealed to the product. They already
know the mechanism of my product. They
already know everything behind it,
right? They have a strong desire to buy
it, but they have these objections. We
need to show them like what this is
going to change in their life. And we
need to make it so that if they don't
take action, it feels worse than if they
did take action and they didn't like
what they got. Right? And a lot of those
principles are again from breakthrough
advertising. I've talked about this very
often on my YouTube and in all the
likeformational things that I've done.
Very helpful along with I just send them
straight to the PDP because now they're
ready to buy. They're really warm. So,
um yeah, that's that's pretty much how
we use this [\h__\h] this funnel, um
funnel, okay, whatever, and leaned into,
you know, this new winning angle that I
had. And then I was like, okay, wait,
great. Like, we can take, you know, we
we can, you know, use this in an ad
account level to then, you know, just
increase the overall performance of the
ad account, you know, increase the
overall performance of this brand. And
that's exactly what happened, you know.
So then, you know, you see number one
slowly start, you know, going down every
day in spend until it almost isn't
spending at all and it's also spending
at a really poor poor rose. And also
mind you, all the these days like these
are days, right? So like the data is a
little bit skewed. Like you want to look
over at like at least a week and
obviously like I'm only spending on
these days I spent like 5k. That's not a
lot of money to spend, right? So like
the data is a little bit skewed. you
know, when you're spending like, let's
say, $50,000 a day, you know, you have
very you very sustainable, you know, uh,
consistent data. Uh, because it's it's
the concept of mean reversion, right?
Like if you just look here, um, if I
draw this line, right, like this, you
can see like this is where the mean's
going to be, right? But some days, this
might be day one, day two, day three,
day four, five, six, seven, eight,
right? Etc. Um, but this is going to be
your net margin, right? So it has to
revert to the mean and you know some
days you're going to see like you know
like it's the ROS will be up it'll be
down and it'll up it'll be down. That's
why you have to look over at least like
a week right and so you see kind of like
this rise right here 2.47 and then the
following day 1.9 right and you're like
okay like that that isn't great or like
you see but you have to understand like
you know we're looking at very small
amounts of data here. Um, but yeah,
guys, I just want to quickly talk about
I know this is a shorter video than I
typically make, but yeah, I want to talk
about how this, you know, [\h__\h] I
leaned into the winning ad angle and I
was like, "Oh, wait. This let me break
down the ad. Like, what am I missing?"
Oh, [\h__\h] Let's do that. So, yeah. Peace
out, everybody. Follow me on Instagram
if you aren't already. Peace out. Oh,
and join join the [\h__\h] Okay, on my
bio in my Instagram bio, you're going to
see this thing. It says like Fchani
Commerce. Join that and then it's like a
DM chat with me and you and I can talk
to you, but you can't talk to me because
it's [\h__\h] cool. Like you literally
join a chat and it's just me talking to
you and you can't talk back and you had
to [\h__\h] deal with it. It's kind of
fire. All right guys, that's all I got.